{
    "subject": "Victor_Salva",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Jeepers_Creepers_2",
    "human_readable": "Victor Salva directed Jeepers Creepers 2.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9627329707145691,
            "question": "Besides Jeepers Creepers 2, what other films has Victor Salva directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9104234576225281,
            "question": "Jeepers Creepers 2 was directed by whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089154601097107,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Jeepers Creepers 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967822551727295,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Jeepers Creepers 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7316933870315552,
            "question": "Name the director of the horror movie Jeepers Creepers 2."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7013716697692871,
            "question": "What type of movie is Jeepers Creepers 2?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6899164915084839,
            "question": "What film is associated with the director Victor Salva?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5545673966407776,
            "question": "Victor Salva is known for directing which horror film sequel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5155720710754395,
            "question": "Is Victor Salva known for directing horror movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4623660743236542,
            "question": "Which movie did Victor Salva direct that had a sequel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Salva directed Jeepers Creepers 2.",
            "html": "yago_7076_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Victor Salva known for directing horror movies?",
            "html": "yago_7076_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Salva is known for directing which horror film sequel?",
            "html": "yago_7076_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is associated with the director Victor Salva?",
            "html": "yago_7076_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7076_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents all mention that Victor Salva wrote and directed Jeepers Creepers 2, with some variations in detail but consistent on this point."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Jeepers Creepers 2\" was written and directed by Victor Salva, which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}